Sorry to drop in on you.
You made all of these?
Wow, that's amazing!
It's nothing special, really.
It is. You're so talented.
Thank you, Dazu. You're too kind.
That's about the extent of my magic power.
I think it's wonderful. Be proud.
Thanks for having me.
Of course. I enjoyed it.
Goodbye, then.
Goodbye.
Listen, we could do this again, if you don't...
All right.
Only one more ingredient.
Could you take over for a moment, Dazu?
Dazu?
Here we are.
Just a dash of mogro leaf powder.
Stir it more gently.
Take your time.
Okay?
Okay.
Much better.
Now they won't get chapped.
Thanks a lot, Bo.
Here.
Your turn.
That should be good.
What would I do without you, Dazu?
What happened?
It was their fault.
They kept asking me to show them my catalyst magic.
They wanted me to fail, so they could laugh.
He looked worried and asked if I was okay.
But I know he found it amusing.
That's how they are.
Every one of them.
But you're different.
And so are you.
Ow.
Try to be strong.
It should heal up soon.
Thank you.
Sure thing.
Hey, it's all right.
Hm.
I always thought I was alone in life.
But now, I realize that's not true.
Since birth, I had lived in a world where people like me never saw the sunlight.
All of us were so weak and fragile.
But, even so, we existed.
It's all right.
That's theión.
Because they're so weak.
It's not like there is a distance.
Things like it's theirçeaph, they're firm.
Things like it to your god.
I'll wait and see if itsplay is상.
And now, everything it is AFT.
And then, we'll go over the面
We will split the world
It's unlike a diamond.
A chat?
We have nothing to say to you.
Aw, come on, don't be like that.
Isn't that guy a magic knight's captain?
I bet he's here to arrest us.
We're right on the border.
Does he have the power to do that?
No way!
I won't let them take me!
Not now! I have to make it into Spade!
So do I!
Keep moving!
You'll never catch us!
Wait a sec.
We're not here to arrest you.
There's no time to delay, right?
Come on!
Ow, that hurt!
Noelle!
Nero!
After them!
No!
It's alright.
We still have the five-leaf grimoire.
With this...
We'll be fine.
Hey, Captain Yami!
Give me your hands.
Huh?
So, boss.
Are we gonna go stop them, or...?
I don't see any reason to hurry.
Oh, hey!
Look up there!
A couple of little birdies have come to our rescue.
It's Captain Foygolion!
And...
That nice chubby guy who makes doors!
And there's my brother!
We're just in time.
Their numbers have increased.
Everyone!
Please listen to what we have to say!
Listen to the magic knights?
Everyone!
Send me all your mana!
Concentrate!
Okay, Dazu!
Right!
For Dazu!
Take mine as well!
To Dazu!
I had thought we might get through to them, but...
Seems not.
After the things they've been through, they're not likely to trust the magic knights.
Hmm?
What now?
What the hell?
She's using catalyst magic. It probably has an effect on the mana in the surrounding area.
We're close to a strong magic region. Gathering everyone's power must have summoned this beast from there.
Thanks for the explanation. Now, what to do?
I can't believe I was able to bring that monster here. If I can do that, then...
Dazoo!
Clean magic! Exploding fireball!
Aaaaaah!
Are you okay?
Um... yes.
Sealing magic. Closed sorrow.
You healed me.
They didn't rush toward us to grab the grimoire. They were trying... to save our lives.
They were trying to save our lives.
Play magic! Ignis Cormna!
Mercury magic.
Silver bullet.
The bullet.
Dark magic.
Dark cloak.
Lightless flash.
Mercury magic.
Dark cloak.
Lightless flash.
Mercury magic.
Silver shining regal spear.
Lightless flash.
Mercury magic.
Silver shining regal spear.
Fall.
Flame spirit magic.
Salamander's breath.
Dark magic.
Dark cloak.
Black flame.
Well, looks like he's had enough.
Wow. They're so powerful.
So this is what the magic knights can do.
I don't believe it.
After all the magic power I collected.
It's over.
We failed.
We can't stand up to them!
Oh, that's for nothing!
How do you think we'll be punished?
Listen.
You guys have got the wrong idea here.
He's right.
It's not our intention to take you into custody.
We just want to talk with you.
Talk with us?
Roger Dodger, sir!
I'll get things rolling right away!
Hey, wait a second!
Is that who I think it is?
The captain of the Golden Dawn!
That's him!
William Bungens!
The hero himself!
Those who live their lives in shadow.
There's the man of the hour.
Thanks for fitting us into your busy schedule, Hotshot.
I'll do anything to aid this kingdom.
After all, I still need to attend.
I'm glad you're here.
But did you really have to bring the Honorable Judge
stick in the mud, too?
You're one of our best.
Good thing you're safe.
We didn't come here to punish anyone.
If I'm correct, you are heading toward the Spade Kingdom.
But you haven't yet crossed the border.
Which means, that as of this moment you haven't committed a crime.
That said, if we asked you to turn around and go home,
I'm sure you'd refuse.
You may not realize it, but we Magic Knights do understand your plight.
So please, will you allow us a bit of time to help you?
We'll do what we can to assuage your doubts.
I don't know what to say.
We shouldn't trust them.
Why would they care about us?
He's right. They're just a bunch of nobles and royalty.
But that's not...
True, as you can see.
The Magic Knights have got plenty of high-class, highfalutin' snobs on the roster.
But we're actually a lot more of a mixed bag than you might expect.
Just look at the Black Bulls.
We got an ex-con.
A guy whose folks disowned him.
A creepy loner.
A royal family's black sheep.
Someone who was alone for a real long time.
Some commoners.
And don't forget me, the foreigner.
When I came to this kingdom, I couldn't even speak the language. I was totally cut off.
The point is, I understand where you guys are coming from.
You've endured great injustice.
And that... is what pushed you over the edge.
We regret that we weren't able to help you more in the past.
It wasn't because we didn't care.
No, Sal.
I swear to you all upon the House of Vermillion.
If I can rid the world of this imbalance, then I will do so.
Now please, return to your homes, and await the day when we have fulfilled this solemn promise.
Mark my words.
The magic knights will strive to shine the light of hope into the darkness!
Captain Vajras!
Look at his face!
I am not so different from you.
I was treated terribly, because of my face.
Then I met the man we know as the Wizard King, Julius Novacrono.
He was kind enough to take me in and look past my unsightly appearance.
He accepted me just the way I was, and gave me a place where I could truly belong.
I owe all that I have to Lord Julius.
And I'll follow his example.
We'll create a place you can live happily, where you can see the sunlight.
So please, if you're able to, just this one time, I want you to believe in the magic knights.
That does sound good.
If they're really going to help make life better for us, can't hurt to try.
Yeah, I say we listen. Let's trust them.
Okay.
Now then.
Dazu Tayak, Bo Nocte, and the rest of the Devil Believers.
You're a separate matter.
You abducted two people.
Incited a riot in the capital.
And...
Let's not forget Cowboy Carillion, Onobi Sinho, and Siona Caverly.
We suspect you may have killed those three.
All right. That's your cue, buddy.
For all these transgressions, you are to be judged.
There's a heavy price for the things you've done.
Very well. If you want to arrest us, then I'll blow you all away!
Don't even waste your time.
But we came so far.
Yes, we did.
Dazu!
I'm sorry, but who said anything about arresting you two?
You think we'll simply throw you in jail?
Foolish.
As I told you, my intention is to judge you.
Therefore, by my righteous power...
I exile you from this land.
Righty-o, sir! Leave it to me!
Both of you, leave the Clover Kingdom at once.
Dazu!
Where we go next, is up to us. It's our path. We're done letting other people decide our fate for us.
As you wish.
Does that mean...
Hmm.
Osta.
My grimoire.
Hey! Wait up!
Hey! Wait up! One day, I'm gonna be the Wizard King! And then I'll create a new Clover Kingdom! Better than what we have now! A place where everyone can understand each other! And laugh together!
So if you leave, promise me that whether you're near or far away, you'll be watching. That way you'll know.
Goodbye, Asta. I wish that I could've been more like you.
We're sorry. Please tell Marie that as well.
So we're left with no grimoire and no hostages. All we have now is each other. If we're being honest, there's almost no chance of us coming out of this alive. But despite all that, I...
I...
We should go.
Right.
Yes.
We'll be joining them. We're leaving this kingdom. But still... In the future, if you fail to create real change...
This will happen again.
Other groups like us will rise from the shadows. Over and over.
It's over.
Bo. Tazu.
The scales that have tipped into darkness must be balanced back toward the light. Isn't that right, Cobwe? Justice should reign supreme in this kingdom.
Come on.
Okay.
I have committed a sin. Several, actually.
that night, I killed my husband and my mother-in-law. They were awful people.
they were awful people in their hearts they always mocked me and looked down upon me
but they never said anything outwardly or let it show on their faces
truthfully i could have lived my whole life pretending that i didn't notice
but then
don't worry i'll save you i swear please get us out and hurry or we'll die
come on dazu good for nothing wench
i've had enough
just die
i never felt an ounce of regret over what happened
i gave those two exactly what they deserved
i'm sure the burn scar that i got from him will fade as time goes by
but
the scars in my heart from enduring years of ridicule
i'll probably have those for life
more than that
even now that they're dead
the flames of vengeance that engulf my soul will burn forever
which is why i
or rather we must reach the spade kingdom at any cost
so that we can obtain the devil's power
this kingdom is embroiled in chaos and the threat of the devil still looms
black clover page 149
two things we need to find
it's always darkest before the dawn
isn't that right my prince
did you
we